seenotice.com 2007-12-18

# Privacy Policy - SeeNotice Classifieds

To protect your privacy, seenotice.com follows the following principles for customer privacy and data protection. **  
:. WHY WE OBTAIN INFORMATION**

> We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a new user profile on the site to use specific features available only to registered users.
> 
> The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to use by not having you enter information more than once. We may also periodically use your information to alert you to updated information and other new services from seenotice.com.
> 
> If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of seenotice.com. But you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.  
> 

**  :. REGISTERED USER PROFILES**

> When you register, your information is protected by use of a password which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password which is neither common or known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password.
> 
> If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.
> 
> We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the "my profile" link provided on our system, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on seenotice.com, your information stays with you.

**  :. NOTICE TO PARENTS**

> Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.
